# **ADENIYI BELLA**

#### CIVIL ENGINEER/SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+49 1789703022

in <u>linkedin</u>

✓ adeniyibella@gmail.com

Github

2

Berlin, Germany

<u>Portfolio</u>

### PROFILE

A Civil Engineer with many years of experience in the construction industry. I took up software development to help in solving some of the challenges faced in the construction industry. The knowledge gained is very much applicable in other professional industries.

### **EDUCATION**

#### CAREER FOUNDRY SCHOOL, BERLIN

07.2022 -

Fullstack Dev.

01.2023

 Project based, practice oriented, remote, collaborative coding training

#### TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY MUNICH

04.2020 -11.2022

M.Sc. Civil Engineering

 Thesis Topic: LPG or RDF as graph data for modelling construction data

# RECENT EXPERIENCE

#### **WOLFF & MUELLER GMBH, STUTTGART**

12.2021 -Present

#### JavaScript Developer/Process Automation

- Introduced code quality checks with linters into our workflow. This improved the readability of codes, and ensured a standard is followed across board.
- Switched the code base from jQuery to react framework and synchronous to async JS. This ensured that we could switch to the new version of the SaaS product the team relied on.
- Automated a lot of manual processes which helped to improve the workflow, user's experience, and worker's performances.

#### **TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY MUNICH**

10.2020 -10.2021

#### **Research Assistant**

- I worked with a group of Ph.D. researchers on the topic of 3D scanning of buildings and applying AI in construction.
- Created building models in blender, labelled them into different classes, and fed the classes to a ML model for semantic segmentation and classification of the classes.
- Created a script in python that helped to optimize the number of scanning points required for a 3D laser scanner.

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- JavaScript/HTML/CSS
- React/React native/Redux
- Node JS/Express framework
- TypeScript
- SQL
- MongoDB
- DESITE BIM
- Al Quality assurance

# PERSONNAL SKILLS

- Fast Learning
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Stress Tolerance
- Leadership
- Team Work

# **LANGUAGES**

- ENGLISH Native
- GERMAN A2

Berlin, Adeniyi Bella

Location, Signature